studyplaces.com 2012-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Studyplaces

**Privacy Policy**

This website – www.studyplaces.com (hereinafter referred to as "Site") is owned and operated by StudyPlaces Inc. We are committed to maintaining your confidence and trust with respect to the information we collect from you. This privacy policy sets forth what information we collect about you, how we use your information, and the choices you have about how we use your information.

**Collection of Information Provided By Your Browser and Through Use of Cookies**

This Site automatically collects information on our server logs from your web browser regarding your use of the Site. Examples of information we collect automatically from all users include the Internet Protocol ("IP") address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; and full Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") click stream data, including date and time, and content you viewed or searched for on the Site.

This Site also collects information through the use of "cookies." Cookies are anonymous, unique alphanumeric identifiers sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. The type of information we collect as a result of a cookie being stored on your computer is specific to your computer. We use "session" cookies to collect information about your use of the Site (e.g., whether you are logged in) and to give you a more personalized browsing experience and help you navigate the Site more efficiently from page to page. These cookies are temporary and are deleted when you close your browser. We use "persistent" cookies to gather statistical information about repeat usage from your computer or workstation.

We collect and use, and may from time to time supply third parties with, this information only as collective or aggregated user data for the purposes of usage analysis, quality control and administering and improving the Site.

You can prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or disable cookies altogether by accessing your browser's preferences menu. If you choose to disable cookies altogether, you can use the Site but will not be able to register, login to the Site with a personal User Name and Password, or make use of the advanced personalization features of the Site, although the basic features and functionality offered to unregistered users of the Site will be possible to use.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

We sometimes request users of the Site to provide personal information. The information collected from a user is strictly voluntary and may include but is not restricted to contact information such as the user's name, e-mail address, and postal address.

In order to access certain content and to make use of the full functionality and advanced personalization features of the Site such as My StudyPlaces, College Speak, etc. we ask you to register and obtain a personal User Name and Password. You may be prompted to register when you:

  * Choose the "Sign up" link from the home page or login screens
  * Use personalization features such as My StudyPlaces
  * Discuss in a forum
  * Post a blog
  * Other unlisted functionality which may be incorporated / updated from time to time

The information collected from the registration form that is presented to users when they choose to register may include contact information such as the user's name, gender, e-mail address, contact details, postal address, profession and country.

Information collected by Site during registration also includes but is not restricted to Educational Information including preferred educational courses and destinations, education level, marks obtained, expected year of admission and the profile of the registrant (student/parent).

The Site reserves the right to use the user information collected during the registration process or otherwise to use for carrying out its own analysis and research. The Site also reserves the right to provide this information to its business partners / relevant third party for any consideration, including monetary gains.

The Site also reserves the right to contact the user based upon the information provided. This contact may be initiated by any of the possible means on the basis of the information provided by the student at registration or through any other mode of contact.

Any user not agreeable to the aforementioned policy shall not register himself/herself with the site. By registering with the site or by the way of filling up any form requiring user information, the user is deemed to have agreed to this privacy policy of the Site.

The terms of this privacy policy are subject to change from time to time without any prior notice.
